// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
//MEDIUM JS 
let questions = [


{
    numb:1,
    question:"Which of the following keywords is used to define a variable in Javascript?",
    answer:"C.Both A and B",
    options:[
    "A.var",
    "B.let",
    "C.Both A and B",
    "D.None of the above",
    ]
},

{
    numb:2,
    question:"What keyword is used to check whether a given property is valid or not?",
    answer:"A. in",
    options:[
    "A. in",
    "B. is in",
    "C. exists",
    "D. lies",
    ]
},

{
    numb:3,
    question:"What is the use of the <noscript> tag in javascript?",
    answer:"A. The contents are displayed by non-JS-based browsers",   
    options:[
    "A. The contents are displayed by non-JS-based browsers",
    "B. Clears all the cookies and cache",
    "C. Both A and B",
    "D. None of the above",
    ]
},

{
    numb:4,
    question:"What will the following code output:console.log(3*'abc')?",
    answer:"C. NaN",
    options:[
    "A. 0",
    "B. 'abcabcabc' ",
    "C. NaN",
    "D. SyntaxError",
    ]
},

{
    numb:5,
    question:"What does the Javascript function call apply() do?",
    answer:"A. Invokes a function with a given this value and arguments provided as an array",
    options:[
    "A. Invokes a function with a given this value and arguments provided as an array",
    "B. Invokes a function once for each element in an array",
    "C. Adds new items to the end of an array",
    "D. Sorts the elements of an array",
    ]
},

{
    numb:6,
    question:"What is the correct way to write an is statement in Javascript?",
    answer:"D. if(x==5)",
    options:[
    "A. if x=5" ,
    "B. if x==5" ,
    "C. if(x=5)",
    "D. if(x==5)",
    ]
},

{
    numb:7,
    question:"What will the following code output: console.log(10%3)?",
    answer:"B. 1",
    options:[
    "A. 3",
    "B. 1",
    "C. 0.33333333333333333",
    "D. 0",
    ]
},

{
    numb:8,
    question:"What will the following code output console.log('Hello'+5)?",
    answer:"A. Hello5",
    options:[
    "A. Hello5",
    "B. Hello+5",
    "C. Error",
    "D. hello5",
    ]
},

{
    numb:9,
    question:"What does the 'return' statement do in a Javascript function?",
    answer:"A. Terminates the function and returns a value to the calling code",
    options:[
    "A. Terminates the function and returns a value to the calling code",
    "B. Executes the function immediately",
    "C. Logs a message to the console",
    "D. Declares a new varaiable",
    ]
},

{
    numb:10,
    question:"What will the following code output: console.log(10=='10')?",
    answer:"A. True",
    options:[
    "A. True",
    "B. False",
    "C. SyntaxError",
    "D. Error",
    ]
},

{
    numb:11,
    question:"Which operatoris used for eponentiation in Javascript?",
    answer:"B. **",
    options:[
    "A. ^",
    "B. **",
    "C. %",
    "D. ^^",
    ]
},

{
    numb:12,
    question:"What will the following code output: console.log(0==false)",
    answer:"A. True",
    options:[
    "A. True",
    "B. False",
    "C. Error",
    "D. 0",
    ]
},

{
    numb:13,
    question:"What is the result of the following expression: '10'+ 5 ?",
    answer:"B. '105' ",
    options:[
    "A. 15",
    "B. '105' ",
    "C. 105",
    "D. Error",
    ]
},

{
    numb:14,
    question:"How do you declare a Javascript object?",
    answer:"C. var myObject{}",
    options:[
    "A. {myObject}",
    "B. object myObject{}",
    "C. var myObject{}",
    "D. myObject=[]",
    ]
},

{
    numb:15,
    question:"What is the Javascript operatorused to assign a value to a variable?",
    answer:"A. =",
    options:[
    "A. =",
    "B. ==",
    "C. :=",
    "D. =>",
    ]
},
  

  
];